<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>hax.camp</title>
  <link href="https://hax.camp/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <subtitle>HAXcamp</subtitle>
  <updated>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</updated>
  <author>
      <name>btopro</name>
  </author>
  <id>https://hax.camp/feed</id>
  <entry>
    <title>Getting here</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/getting-here</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T11:27:25-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</published>
    <summary>hax-camp will be held at the Duke University Bostock Library(Floor 1) on October 7th & 8th 2019.Bostock LibraryTelecom DriveDurham, NC 27710ParkingBryan Center lot is the closest - seehttps</summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/getting-here"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <p>hax-camp will be held at the Duke University <a href="https://naming.library.duke.edu/room/14181">Bostock Librar</a>
y<span style="font-size: var(--haxcms-base-styles-p-font-size, 24px); letter-spacing: var(--haxcms-base-styles-p-letter-spacing, 0.5px); caret-color: var(--hax-color-text);"><a href="https://naming.library.duke.edu/room/14181">(Floor 1)</a>
 on October 7th & 8th 2019.</span></p>
<blockquote class="hax-active"><span style=""><span style="caret-color: rgb(25, 30, 35);"><b>Bostock Library<br/>Telecom Drive<br/>Durham, NC 27710</b>

</span><br/></span></blockquote>
<iframe src="https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d1687.3797126688928!2d-78.9396484850072!3d36.00311075229569!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x89ace6ae3a206b37%3A0xb1b730d7077b2d71!2sTelecom+Dr%2C+Durham%2C+NC+27710!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1565888263939!5m2!1sen!2sus" width="600" height="450" frameborder="0" style="border: 0px; margin: 0px auto; display: block; width: 100%;" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
<h3>Parking</h3>
<p><span style="caret-color: rgb(0, 0, 0);"><span style="">Bryan Center lot is the closest - see
<span id="docs-internal-guid-9fca6db2-7fff-9715-58b8-a2f9a34b7c65" style=""><a href="https://parking.duke.edu/visitor" style="">https://parking.duke.edu/visitor</a>

 for details</span></span></span></p>
<h3 class="hax-active"><span style="caret-color: rgb(0, 0, 0);"><span style=""><span style="">Transportation</span></span></span></h3>
<p><span style="caret-color: rgb(0, 0, 0);"><span style=""><span style="">The <a href="https://www.rdu.com/">Raleigh-Durham International Airport</a>

 is a 25 minute drive from the Duke Library and around a $20-30 cab ride.</span></span></span></p>
<h3><span style="caret-color: var(--hax-color-text);">Hotels</span></h3>
<p><span style="caret-color: rgb(25, 30, 35);">Durham has many hotels in the surrounding area including a few just off campus and one on campus. <a href="https://www.google.com/maps/search/Hotels/@36.0052302,-78.9457881,14.9z/data=!4m14!2m13!3m6!1sHotels!2sTelecom+Dr,+Durham,+NC+27710!3s0x89ace6ae3a206b37:0xb1b730d7077b2d71!4m2!1d-78.9388428!2d36.0031066!5m5!5m4!1s2019-10-06!2i3!4m1!1i1?hl=en-US">Shortcut google link</a>

 to see what's around.</span></p>
 ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Schedule</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/schedule</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-08-15T10:54:37-06:00</published>
    <summary></summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/schedule"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <p>Ex uno Plures</p> ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Registration</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/register</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-05-28T18:59:02-06:00</published>
    <summary>Registration will open the week of August 19th.</summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/register"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <p>Registration will open the week of August 19th.</p>
<meme-maker image-url="https://media1.giphy.com/media/oWjyixDbWuAk8/giphy.gif" top-text="one of us" bottom-text="one of us" style="width: 50%;"></meme-maker>
 ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Convince your boss</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/convince-my-hippo</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-05-28T18:34:09-06:00</published>
    <summary>HiPPO (Highest Paid Person's Opinion) is super important to getting funding to come to HAX camp. Here's some easy reasons they'll be thrilled to send you:Web components can be used in any Content Man</summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/convince-my-hippo"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <p>HiPPO (Highest Paid Person's Opinion) is super important to getting funding to come to HAX camp. Here's some easy reasons they'll be thrilled to send you:</p>
<ul><li>Web components can be used in any Content Management System (CMS) or Front End library you use currently!</li>

<li>Web components augment existing workflows, helping your team to work smarter, not harder, by building reusable, cross project components</li>
<li>Eventually, web components CAN replicate your front end stack, but only if you want them to.</li>
<li>Web components are a standard, they are only going to improve and increase in adoption (less framework retraining / churn).</li>
<li>Experts from some of the largest web component libraries will be there.</li>
<li>Web components reduce costs, improve transparency, are highly accessible, and generally just make web development fun again (and you want happy employees don't you!?)</li>
</ul>
<meme-maker image-url="https://media2.giphy.com/media/jKgPsc0ZlqNTa/giphy.gif" top-text="HAX.camp?!" bottom-text="Totes you should go!" style="width: 75%;"></meme-maker>
 ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Whats an Unconference?</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/schedule/unconference</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-05-28T18:22:36-06:00</published>
    <summary>If you&#39;ve never been, they are awesome. here&#39;s a basic definition from Wikipedia.Effectively, the people who show up form the schedule and go from there. HAX camp is not a pure Unconference as there</summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/schedule/unconference"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <p>If you've never been, they are awesome. here's a basic definition from Wikipedia.</p>
<wikipedia-query show-title="show-title" search="Unconference" render-as="content" style="width: 100%;" search-response="[object Object]"></wikipedia-query>
<p>Effectively, the people who show up form the schedule and go from there. HAX camp is not a pure Unconference as there are <b><i>some</i>
 </b>
planned session items but it is largely up to the group in attendance as to what direction it goes.</p>
<p>If 2 people showed up wanting to talk about how StencilJS elements data binding works in React? Then that'd be enough to have a conversation and call a session. If everyone wanted to learn about the Theming layer in HAXcms, that'd be on the schedule.</p>
<p>The only requirements of the Unconference are..</p>
<ul><li>Be respectful, but vote with your feet. If a conversation is not the one you wanted, find one you do. Participants are empowered to form the optimal conversations to make the most of the day for them.</li>

<li>Keep on point. If a session was called about a topic, try and stick to it unless the group wants to wander to other topics.</li>
<li>It must be related to <i>Web components</i>
 in some fashion.</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="caret-color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">Our Unconference Format</span></p>
<ul><li><span style="caret-color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">We will start the day with 30 minutes of saying who we are and what we are interested in learning from the day.</span></li>
<li><span style="caret-color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">We will then have 10 minutes for people to build the schedule by filling out large poster cards. After which time everyone who wishes to call a session gives an elevator pitch for it.</span></li>
<li><span style="caret-color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">We will then take 10 minutes and build the schedule on the wall.</span></li>
<li>We have now created a conference and the day commences</li>
</ul>
 ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Why attend</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/why-attend</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-05-28T18:22:36-06:00</published>
    <summary>Why should I comeLearn from others about how they are using web componentsLearn about PatternFly Elements from their web component prosLearn about All things HAXTHEWeb and have community </summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/why-attend"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <h3 class="hax-active">Why should I come</h3>
<ul><li>Learn from others about how they are using web components<br/></li>
<li>Learn about <a href="https://www.patternfly.org/">PatternFly Elements</a>
 from their web component pros</li>





<li>Learn about All things <a href="https://github.com/elmsln/haxcms">HAXTHEWeb</a>
 and have community with other users</li>





<li>See the future of OER with practical applications of web components</li>
<li>Get trained on using Web components and different libraries</li>





</ul>
<h2>Who should come?</h2>
<meme-maker image-url="https://live.staticflickr.com/4481/37249987684_d9efac206b_b.jpg" top-text="Everybody" bottom-text="everybody!" style="width: 25%;"></meme-maker>
<p>No but <a href="https://homestarrunner.com/">"sewe-us-lee you guys"</a>

, everyone should come to HAX camp! HAX camp is for all skill levels. The only requirement is that you are interested in web components and learning more about them!</p>
 ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Details</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/details</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T11:30:35-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-05-28T18:20:22-06:00</published>
    <summary>When is it?October 7th and 8th, 2019Where is it?Duke UniversityBostock LibraryTelecom DriveDurham, NC 27710Duke has graciously offered to host the first ever HAX Camp to increase knowled</summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/details"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <h3>When is it?</h3>
<p>October 7th and 8th, 2019<br/></p>
<h3>Where is it?</h3>
<blockquote class="hax-active"><span style=""><span style="caret-color: rgb(25, 30, 35);"><b>Duke University<br/>Bostock Library<br/>Telecom Drive<br/>Durham, NC 27710</b>



</span><br/></span></blockquote>
<html-block style="display: block; width: 100%;">
<iframe src="https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d1687.3797126688928!2d-78.9396484850072!3d36.00311075229569!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x89ace6ae3a206b37%3A0xb1b730d7077b2d71!2sTelecom+Dr%2C+Durham%2C+NC+27710!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1565888263939!5m2!1sen!2sus" width="600" height="450" frameborder="0" style="border: 0px; margin: 0px auto; display: block; width: 100%;" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>


</html-block>
<p>Duke has graciously offered to host the <i>first ever</i>
 HAX Camp to increase knowledge sharing among web component developers and those who would most benefit from them.</p>
 ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Code of conduct</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/coc</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-05-28T18:20:22-06:00</published>
    <summary>Code of Conduct.Don't troll people by showing VDOM and everything will be cool.No but seriously...Our pledgeIn the interest of fostering an open and welcoming environment, we as organizers pledge</summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/coc"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <p>Code of Conduct.</p>
<p>Don't troll people by showing VDOM and everything will be cool.</p>
<p>No but seriously...</p>
<h2>Our pledge</h2>
<p>
In the interest of fostering an open and welcoming environment, we as organizers pledge to making participation in our event as awesome as we possibly can.
It is the policy of hax-camp to maintain an environment free of harassment and free of discrimination against any person because of age, race, color, ancestry, national origin, religion,
creed, service in the uniformed services (as defined in state and federal law), veteran status, sex, sexual orientation,
marital or family status, pregnancy, pregnancy-related conditions, physical or mental disability, gender, perceived gender,
gender identity, genetic information or political ideology.
</p>
<p>Discriminatory conduct and harassment will not be tolerated at our event.</p>
<h2 class="hax-active">Our standards</h2>
<h3 class="hax-active">How you will keep our community awesome:</h3>
<ul><li>Showing empathy to everyone</li>

<li>Being respectful of differing viewpoints and experiences</li>

<li>Accepting constructive criticism</li>

<li>Acting in the best interests of the community</li>
</ul>
<h3 class="hax-active">Behaviors our community will not tolerate:</h3>
<ul><li>Harassment - public or private</li>

<li>Unwelcome sexual attention or advances</li>

<li>Trolling - derogatory interactions and personal or political attacks</li>

<li>Doxing - publishing others' private information without permission</li>

<li>Any conduct reasonably considered inappropriate in professional settings</li>
</ul>
<h2 class="hax-active">Our responsibilities</h2>
<p>
Event organizers are responsible for clarifying the standards of acceptable behavior and are expected
to take appropriate and fair corrective action in response to any instances of unacceptable behavior.

Organizers have the right to remove or modify comments, commits, code, documentation,
issues, and other contributions that are not aligned to this Code of Conduct.
</p>
<h3>Scope</h3>
<p>
This Code of Conduct applies both within project spaces and in spaces where an individual is 
representing the project or its community. Examples of representing a project or community include using 
an official project e-mail address, posting via an official social media account, or acting as an official 
representative at an event. Representation of a project may be further defined and clarified 
by project maintainers.
</p>
<p>The hax-camp Code of Conduct applies to anyone involved in the event, including event organizers.
</p>
<h3>Enforcement</h3>
<p>
Instances of behavior which violates the hax-camp Code of Conduct may be reported by contacting 
project leadership at bryan@waxam.io. The event leadership will review and investigate all complaints, and will 
respond in a way that it deems appropriate. The event leadership is obligated to maintain 
confidentiality with regard to the reporter of an incident. Further details of specific enforcement policies 
may be posted separately.
</p>
<p>The hax-camp Code of Conduct was originally produced in the United States of America and operates based on US legal norms
which presumes innocence until guilt is proven.
</p>
<h3>CoC attribution</h3>
<p>This Code of Conduct has been forked from the Contributor Covenant, version 1.4, available at http://contributor-covenant.org/version/1/4</p>
 ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>hax-camp</title>
    <id>https://hax.camp/hax-camp</id>
    <updated>2019-08-15T10:57:14-06:00</updated>
    <published>2019-05-28T18:08:49-06:00</published>
    <summary>hax-camp is a first of its kind unconference dedicated to all thing Web components.Have you made something cool with Web components and want to show off? BRING ITDo you want to learn more</summary>
    <link href="https://hax.camp/hax-camp"/>
    
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[ <p>hax-camp is a first of its kind <i><b><a href="schedule/unconference">unconference</a>

</b>



</i>



 dedicated to all thing Web components.</p>
<meme-maker style="width: 50%; margin: 0px auto; display: block;" image-url="https://media3.giphy.com/media/oGO1MPNUVbbk4/giphy.gif" top-text="hax-camp" bottom-text="I see what you did" imageurl="https://media3.giphy.com/media/oGO1MPNUVbbk4/giphy.gif" toptext="BC U new" bottomtext="it wood hapn" dataeditable="" datahaxray="Meme"></meme-maker>
<p>Have you made something cool with Web components and want to show off? BRING IT</p>
<p>Do you want to learn more about web components? BRING THAT TOO.</p>
<p>Curious about all things HAXTheWeb. WELL WE WILL BE THERE.</p>
<p>HAX Camp is dedicated to all the parts of the stack that relate to HAX.</p>
 ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>